shopperreports.com 2012-12-29

# ShopperReports.com - Privacy Statement

This Privacy Policy applies to Pinball Corp's ShopperReports browser add-on and the shopperreports.com website ("Website"). 

We believe your privacy is very important and we're committed to protecting your privacy. Our Privacy Policy for the ShopperReports program is simple: 

ShopperReports is a browser add-on that can be downloaded from [www.shopperreports.com](http://www.shopperreports.com/)

**What we do:**

  * **The Service** \- The ShopperReports browser add-on is designed to help you compare products and prices while you shop online. While shopping online, ShopperReports will detect the product you are looking at and automatically search thousands of vendors for better prices. Alternative prices will then be displayed in a browser side bar. 
  * **Limited List** \- We maintain a limited list of pre-examined domains determined by our professional team to be shopping or travel related websites. Such lists are updated from time to time. The browser add-on becomes active only when visiting such domains or when manually triggered by you. 
  * **Transferred Information** \- When visiting one of the domains on the limited list, the ShopperReports add-on will send the product information you are viewing to it's servers in order to search for alternatives. 
  * **Non Personal Information** \- All data transferred to our servers by the browser add-on is anonymous and does not contain any Personally Identifiable Information ("PII"), like email, name, address etc. 

**What ShopperReports doesn't do:**

  * ShopperReports does not collect any PII about you within the browser add-on. 
  * ShopperReports does not trade or rent PII to third parties. 
  * ShopperReports does not track the websites you visit, unless they exist in our limited list of ecommerce and travel sites. 
  * ShopperReports does not present popups on your computer. 
  * ShopperReports does not present any other form of display advertising. 
  * ShopperReports does not change the default search of your browser, your home page, nor any other settings of your browser. 

**What information does** ShopperReports **collect?**

_Anonymous Information_

The information sent by the ShopperReports add-on to the ShopperReports servers is anonymous and may include: 

  * Your Internet Protocol (IP) Address 
  * The Full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) of the web page you are visiting 
  * General information about your browser and your computer's operating system 
  * Product information as taken from the page's HTML you currently view 
  * Your ShopperReports cookie number 
  * The date and time the above information is logged 

ShopperReports also collects and stores the following usage statistics: 

  * What is clicked on the ShopperReports add-on sidebar 
  * The amount of time the service is used during each session 
  * The keyword searches within the add-on search box, and the alternative results that are presented during a session. 

If you are visiting our Website ([www.shopperreports.com](http://www.shopperreports.com/)), we collect the following information: 

  * The URL of the web page which you arrived from 
  * The date and time of each page you view 
  * The information of any ad that brought you to our Website 
  * Computer and connection information. 

If the URL of the page you came from contains any PII, ShoperReports will not attempt to determine your identity by analyzing the URL in any way. When arriving to the ShopperReports Website, the IP address of your computer is recorded by the web server, an automated information collection, as done by any web server. ShopperReports does not share this information with any third parties. 

_Personally Identifiable Information_

In the Website, if you contact us through the "Contact us" page, you are required to provide your e-mail address and, optionally, name and phone number, so that we may be able to respond to your inquiry. This PII is not used in any manner other than to contact you regarding your inquiry. If the PII mentioned above changes, you may correct or update it by emailing our customer support at [support@shopperreports.com](mailto:support@shopperreports.com) or by contacting us through postal mail to the contact information listed at the bottom of this page. 

**What do we do with the information we collect?**

The information sent to the ShopperReports servers is used to identify the product you are currently viewing. Based on ShopperReports' analysis of this information, ShopperReports will search for alternative vendors to present to you with the ShopperReports add-on. In addition, ShopperReports analyzes its logs of usage statistics in order to continuously improve the quality of the service. 

If you provide limited PII by contacting ShopperReports through the "Contact us" web page, we will not correlate or link such PII to any data stored on our servers. 

**Do we share the information we collect?**

_Anonymous Information_

ShopperReports works with third-party content providers to serve comparative offers. We share the anonymous information with such companies in order to retrieve and present alternative product pricing and information. ShopperReports does not place any restrictions on usage of this anonymous information by its third-party partners. 

_Personally Identifiable Information_

We do not share any Personally Identifiable Information with any third parties, except in these rare circumstances: 

As required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process. 

In the event that our company sells substantially all of its assets, undergoes a corporate restructuring or is acquired, the service and all information collected by the service would be transferred to the acquiring party. In any such transfer the information would remain subject to any terms and conditions applicable to the service at the time the information was collected, including the terms of this Privacy Policy and any amendments thereto. 

**Cookies**

Upon visiting [www.shopperreports.com](http://www.shopperreports.com/), a cookie is sent to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. This cookie assigns your web browser with a unique series of numbers, letters, or characters that enables ShopperReports' servers to recognize and identify your web browser. This information helps ShopperReports to customize your online experience and make it more convenient for you when using the service or the Website. 

**Age requirement and children's privacy**

You must be at least 18 years of age to use the ShopperReports software. By accepting the terms of this agreement and using the software, you represent that you are over the age of 18. If you are under 18 years of age, but are at least 13 years of age or older, your parent or legal guardian must accept the terms of this agreement on your behalf. We do not knowingly solicit or collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13\. If we nevertheless receive personally identifiable information from an individual who indicates that he or she is, or whom we otherwise have reason to believe is under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our systems. 

**Third party sites**

While we try to link only to websites that we believe share our respect for privacy, please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements and terms of use of such other third parties before you provide them with personal information since their Privacy Policy and terms of use shall apply to such activity. 

**Software updates**

The browser add-on is designed to check for the availability of updates to ensure that you enjoy the latest improvements. When the browser add-on checks for the availability of updates, anonymous information about the version is sent to our web server. This information is used only to determine whether a new version is available for download. 

**Opt-out / Choices/ Changes**

To temporarily snooze or set usage rules for certain parts of the browser add-on, go to the ShopperReports side bar and click "Snooze". 

**Removal of the ShopperReports add-on**

If you are experiencing a technical problem or other difficulty with the ShopperReports comparative shopping add-on, please contact our support team at [support@shopperreports.com](mailto:support@shopperreports.com). 

**Information security**

ShopperReports undertakes extensive physical, electronic and procedural security measures to protect against loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Your personal and traffic data can only be accessed by authorized employees who need to have access to this data in order to be able to fulfill their given duties. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

ShopperReports is constantly evolving. New features are continuously being added to the Website and software. With these improvements, our Privacy Policy may evolve. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy on the Website. You are encouraged to check this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your use of the service, software or Website after a change has been posted shall be deemed your acceptance of such change. If you do not agree with any change, immediately cease using the service, software or Website. 

**How to contact us about privacy**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Website and service, or your dealings with this Website, you can email us at: [support@shopperreports.com](mailto:support@shopperreports.com)

**This Privacy Policy was last updated on June 11, 2009.**
